Highway Don't Care
歌手：Tim McGraw ft
歌手：Taylor Swift
歌手：Keith Urban
高速公路不在乎
压制：随Feng
我想，你一定摇下了车窗，发丝在脑后飞扬
Bet your window’s down and your hair’s pulled back
我想，你一定不知道，车轮飞驰的节奏
I bet you got no idea you’re going way too fast
努力的不去回想，是哪里出了错
And you’re trying not to think about what went wrong
努力在到达目的地前，不停歇
Trying not to stop til you get where you goin’
努力的保持清醒
Trying to stay awake
所以我想，你一定按下了收音机的播放键
so I bet you turn on the radio
音符飘扬
And the song goes
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
亲爱的，离开你，我无法呼吸
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby, baby
高速公路无法在今夜给你温暖的拥抱
The highway won’t hold you tonight
高速公路感受不到你的心跳
The highway don’t know you’re alive
高速公路不在乎你是否被孤单围绕
The highway don’t care if you’re all alone
但是，我在乎
But I do, I do.
高速公路无法拭去你眼角的泪水
The highway won’t dry your tears
高速公路不需要你的陪伴
The highway don’t need you here
高速公路不在乎你是否驶向家的方向
The highway don’t care if you’re coming home
但是，我在乎
But I do, I do.
我想，你的副驾驶座位上一定摆着一只无法使用的手机
I bet you got a dead cell phone in the shot gun seat
我想，你一定无数次的提起我的名字
Yeah, I bet you’re bending God’s ear talking about me
努力的不让第一滴泪水滑落
You’re trying not to let the first tear fall out
努力的不去想要转身
Trying not to think about turning around
努力的不让自己迷失在乐声中
Trying not to get lost in the sound
可旋律却不停的回响，所以你跟着和
But that song is always on so you sing along
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
亲爱的，离开你，我无法呼吸
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby, baby
高速公路无法在今夜给你温暖的拥抱
The highway won’t hold you tonight
高速公路感受不到你的心跳
The highway don’t know you’re alive
高速公路不在乎你是否被孤单围绕
The highway don’t care if you’re all alone
但是，我在乎
But I do, I do.
高速公路无法拭去你眼角的泪水
The highway won’t dry your tears
高速公路不需要你的陪伴
The highway don’t need you here
高速公路不在乎你是否驶向家的方向
The highway don’t care if you’re coming home
但是，我在乎
But I do, I do.
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
亲爱的，离开你，我无法...
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you bab...
高速公路不在乎
The highway don’t care
但是，我在乎
But I do, I do.
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
亲爱的，离开你，我无法呼吸
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby, baby
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
亲爱的，离开你，我无法呼吸
但是，我在乎
But I do, I do.
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
亲爱的，离开你，我无法呼吸
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby, baby
亲爱的，我的生活不能没有你
I can’t live without you, I can’t live without you baby
压制：随Feng